Hello, English learners.
你好，英语学习者。
Welcome back to EnglishPod.
欢迎回到EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
And I'm Erica.
我是Erica。
And today with Erica, we're bringing you a great lesson about time.
今天和Erica一起，我们为大家带来一堂关于时间的精彩课程。
You need more of it.
你需要更多时间。
We need more time, right?
我们需要更多时间，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
So we're going to be teaching you how you can ask for more time.
所以我们将教你如何请求更多时间。
If you're working on a project at work and you can't finish it on time, you have to ask
如果你在工作中负责一个项目，无法按时完成，你必须向老板请求更多时间。
your boss for more time.
向你的老板请求更多时间。
Right.
没错。
So in our dialogue, Casey needs more time to put together a press kit.
所以在我们的对话中，Casey需要更多时间来准备一个媒体资料包。
What's a press kit?
什么是媒体资料包？
Good question.
好问题。
A press kit is something the marketing department will put together.
媒体资料包是市场部会准备的东西。
Basically pictures, logos, information about the company.
基本上包括图片、标志、公司信息。
So when a newspaper or a magazine wants to write an article about them, so they have
所以当报纸或杂志想写一篇关于他们的文章时，他们已经有准备好的资料可以提供给报纸或杂志。
something already prepared that they could give the newspaper or magazine.
已经准备好的东西，可以给报纸或杂志。
Okay.
好的。
So let's listen to our dialogue for the first time.
那么让我们第一次听我们的对话。
And as always, it's going to be at a normal speed, so it might be a little bit difficult
和往常一样，它会以正常语速进行，所以可能有点难理解。
to understand.
有点难理解。
We'll come back in one minute and tell you about some of the key language.
我们一分钟后回来，告诉你们一些关键语言。
So Casey, how are things going with the photos for the press kit?
那么Casey，媒体资料包的照片进展如何？
Yeah, I've been meaning to talk to you about that.
嗯，我一直想跟你谈谈这件事。
I might need to ask for an extension on that deadline.
我可能需要申请延期。
You've had over a month to get this finalized.
你已经有一个多月的时间来完成这个了。
Why are things delayed?
为什么事情延迟了？
Well, the thing is, we ran into a lot of problems.
嗯，问题是，我们遇到了很多麻烦。
I'm not looking for excuses here.
我不是在找借口。
I just want to get this finished on time.
我只想按时完成这个。
I know.
我知道。
And I apologize for the delay.
我为延迟道歉。
But some things were just beyond my control.
但有些事情超出了我的控制。
I had trouble booking the photographer.
我预约摄影师遇到了困难。
And then Michael was sick for three weeks.
然后Michael病了三周。
So I couldn't include him in the photos.
所以我无法让他参与拍照。
And the design team lost all the files.
而且设计团队丢失了所有文件。
So I had to redo the pictures.
所以我不得不重做照片。
I'm not going to put this off any longer, Casey.
我不能再拖了，凯西。
I want those photos ASAP.
我马上要那些照片。
All right.
好吧。
So Casey is in trouble, I think.
所以凯西有麻烦了，我觉得。
Yeah, I think her boss is pretty upset.
是啊，我觉得她老板很生气。
Yeah.
嗯。
So let's take a look at some of the language that we saw in this dialogue in Language Takeaway.
那我们来看看对话中出现的一些语言点，在语言要点部分。
Language Takeaway.
语言要点。
First word today is deadline.
今天的第一个词是截止日期。
Deadline.
截止日期。
So, Erika, what's a deadline?
那么，埃里卡，什么是截止日期？
It is the last possible date to do something.
就是做某事的最后可能日期。
So for example, when we were in school, our teacher would send us homework and say it
比如，我们上学时，老师布置作业会说
was for Friday.
周五交。
So the deadline was Friday.
所以截止日期就是周五。
Was Friday, right?
是周五，对吧？
Or when you're at work, you have projects that you have to finish by a certain date.
或者工作时，你有项目必须在某个日期前完成。
That's your deadline.
那就是你的截止日期。
Exactly.
没错。
Okay, let's look at our next word.
好的，我们来看下一个词。
Extension.
延期。
So extension and deadline go together, right?
所以延期和截止日期是相关的，对吧？
Exactly.
没错。
If you can't reach your deadline or you can't make your deadline, you must ask for an extension.
如果你无法赶上截止日期，就必须申请延期。
An extension.
延期。
So you ask for more time.
就是要求更多时间。
Yeah.
对。
So extension is moving the deadline in the future.
所以延期就是把截止日期往后推。
Alright, interesting.
好的，有意思。
Let's look at our next word.
我们来看下一个词。
Ran into.
遇到。
Ran into some problems.
遇到了一些问题。
So we ran into some problems in this dialogue.
所以在这个对话中我们遇到了一些问题。
Let's listen to some more examples of run into so we can understand the meaning.
让我们再听一些关于“run into”的例子，这样我们就能理解它的意思了。
Example one.
例子一。
We ran into a storm on our way home.
我们在回家的路上遇到了暴风雨。
Example two.
例子二。
If you're not careful now, you're going to run into a lot of problems later.
如果你现在不小心，以后会遇到很多问题。
Example three.
例子三。
I ran into some trouble with my computer.
我的电脑遇到了一些麻烦。
Okay, good example.
好的，好例子。
So it's clear now, right?
所以现在清楚了吧？
Right.
对。
If you run into problems, you meet some problems.
如果你遇到问题，就是碰到一些问题。
Right.
对。
Many students say it in that way.
很多学生那样说。
I met some problems.
我遇到了一些问题。
Yeah, but that's wrong.
是的，但那是错的。
Right.
对。
So you would say I ran into some problems.
所以你会说“我遇到了一些问题”。
Right.
对。
I met some problems is wrong, wrong, wrong.
“我遇到了一些问题”是错的，错的，错的。
Okay, don't say met some problems.
好的，别说“遇到了一些问题”。
I ran into some problems.
我遇到了一些问题。
I ran into.
我遇到了。
Okay.
好的。
And our last word for language takeaway, delayed.
我们语言学习的最后一个词是“延迟”。
Delayed.
延迟。
So when something is delayed, it's late.
所以当某件事被延迟了，就是晚了。
Late.
晚了。
And the opposite is...
反义词是……
On time.
准时。
So your flight was delayed.
所以你的航班延误了。
Or your flight was on time.
或者你的航班准时了。
The project was delayed.
项目被推迟了。
Or your project was on time.
或者你的项目按时完成了。
Clear.
清楚。
Alright.
好的。
So now let's go back to the dialogue.
现在我们回到对话。
Let's listen to it again.
我们再听一遍。
And this time it will be a little bit slower so you can understand some of these phrases
这次会慢一点，这样你就能理解其中一些短语了。
we just talked about.
我们刚才谈到的。
So Casey, how are things going with the photos for the press kit?
凯西，宣传资料的照片进展如何？
Yeah, I've been meaning to talk to you about that.
嗯，我一直想跟你谈谈这件事。
I might need to ask for an extension on that deadline.
我可能需要申请延期。
You've had over a month to get this finalized.
你有一个多月的时间来完成这件事。
Why are things delayed?
为什么事情会延迟？
Well, the thing is, we ran into a lot of problems.
嗯，问题是，我们遇到了很多麻烦。
I'm not looking for excuses here.
我不是在找借口。
I just want to get this finished on time.
我只想按时完成。
I know.
我知道。
And I apologize for the delay.
我为延迟道歉。
But some things were just beyond my control.
但有些事情超出了我的控制。
I had trouble booking the photographer.
我预约摄影师时遇到了困难。
And then Michael was sick for three weeks so I couldn't include him in the photos.
然后迈克尔病了三个星期，所以我没法让他入镜。
And the design team lost all the files so I had to redo the pictures.
而且设计团队弄丢了所有文件，我不得不重做照片。
I'm not going to put this off any longer, Casey.
我不会再拖延了，凯西。
I want those photos ASAP.
我尽快要那些照片。
Okay, so there were some really useful phrases that we saw in this dialogue.
好的，这段对话中有一些非常有用的短语。
Yeah, some wonderful phrases that you can use when you want to ask for more time.
是的，一些很棒的短语，当你想要更多时间时可以用。
Okay, so let's look at these phrases in Fluency Builder.
好的，我们来看看流利度构建器中的这些短语。
Fluency Builder.
流利度构建器。
Alright, what's our first phrase?
好的，第一个短语是什么？
I've been meaning to talk to you.
我一直想跟你谈谈。
I've been meaning to.
我一直想。
Okay, we have some really great examples of how you can combine I've been meaning to with
好的，我们有一些很好的例子，展示如何将“我一直想”与
different verbs.
不同的动词搭配。
Yeah, let's listen.
是的，我们来听一下。
Example one.
例子一。
I'm sorry I haven't called you yet.
抱歉我还没给你打电话。
I've been meaning to, but I've been busy.
我一直想打，但一直很忙。
Example two.
例子二。
I've been meaning to tell you, but John quit yesterday.
我一直想告诉你，但约翰昨天辞职了。
Example three.
例子三。
I've been meaning to see that film for a while.
我一直想看那部电影，有一阵子了。
I've been meaning to go to that restaurant, but I haven't had time.
我一直想去那家餐厅，但一直没时间。
So you've been wanting to for a long time.
所以你一直想去做，已经很久了。
Right.
对。
I've been thinking about it.
我一直在考虑。
I've been planning to do it.
我一直在计划去做。
But you just haven't done it.
但你还没做。
I haven't done it, maybe because I haven't had time or money.
我没做，可能是因为没时间或没钱。
Okay, good phrase.
好的，好短语。
Our next phrase is beyond my control.
下一个短语是“超出我的控制”。
Beyond my control.
超出我的控制。
It's beyond my control.
这超出了我的控制。
So it means that I can't control it.
意思是说我无法控制它。
You can't do anything about it.
你对此无能为力。
I can't do anything about it.
我对此无能为力。
The weather is beyond my control.
天气超出了我的控制。
Right, or relate with this project because Jane was sick for one month.
对，或者和这个项目有关，因为简病了一个月。
It was beyond my control.
这超出了我的控制。
Okay, it wasn't your fault.
好吧，那不是你的错。
No.
不。
It was my fault.
是我的错。
And our last phrase for fluency builder, put this off.
流利度训练中的最后一个短语是“推迟”。
Put this off.
推迟。
So let's listen to some more examples of put this off before we explain the meaning.
在解释意思之前，我们先听一些关于“推迟”的例子。
Example one.
例子一。
I've been putting off this project for a week and it's due tomorrow.
我把这个项目推迟了一周，明天就要交了。
Example two.
例子二。
Can we put off our meeting until next week?
我们能推迟会议到下周吗？
I'm too busy right now.
我现在太忙了。
Example three.
例子三。
I've been putting off my email all day and now I have 50 messages to respond to.
我一整天都在推迟处理邮件，现在有50条消息要回复。
So Marco, when you put something off, you leave it for later.
所以马可，当你推迟某事时，你把它留到以后做。
Okay.
好的。
Right.
对。
I'm going to write a report today, but I'm going to put it off till tomorrow.
我今天要写报告，但我要推迟到明天。
So you're going to do it tomorrow.
所以你打算明天做。
I'll do it tomorrow.
我明天做。
Okay, so we've seen some really great words and some really good phrases.
好的，我们学到了一些很棒的单词和短语。
So now let's listen to our dialogue for the last time and then we'll come back and talk
现在让我们最后一次听对话，然后回来再聊
some more.
更多内容。
So Casey, how are things going with the photos for the press kit?
凯西，新闻资料包的照片进展如何？
Yeah, I've been meaning to talk to you about that.
嗯，我正想和你谈这件事。
I might need to ask for an extension on that deadline.
我可能需要申请延期。
You've had over a month to get this finalized.
你已经有一个多月的时间来完成这件事了。
Why are things delayed?
为什么事情都延迟了？
Well, the thing is we ran into a lot of problems.
嗯，问题是我们遇到了很多麻烦。
I'm not looking for excuses here.
我不是在找借口。
I just want to get this finished on time.
我只想按时完成这件事。
I know.
我知道。
And I apologize for the delay, but some things were just beyond my control.
我为延迟道歉，但有些事情确实超出了我的控制。
I had trouble booking the photographer and then Michael was sick for three weeks, so
我预约摄影师时遇到了麻烦，然后迈克尔病了三周，所以
I couldn't include him in the photos.
我无法让他参与拍照。
And the design team lost all the files, so I had to redo the pictures.
而且设计团队丢失了所有文件，所以我不得不重做图片。
I'm not going to put this off any longer, Casey.
我不会再拖延了，凯西。
I want those photos ASAP.
我尽快要那些照片。
Well, Marco, do you think that Casey's reasons for being late are good?
嗯，马可，你觉得凯西迟到的理由合理吗？
I think so, because it wasn't really her fault, the whole situation with the photographer.
我觉得合理，因为那真的不是她的错，整件事都是摄影师的问题。
And then one of her co-workers was sick for three weeks.
然后她有个同事病了三周。
It's not really her fault, right?
这真的不是她的错，对吧？
Right, but maybe the boss thinks that she's making excuses.
对，但也许老板觉得她在找借口。
Maybe she's making excuses.
也许她在找借口。
That's really common.
这很常见。
Like, for example, when we were kids, you would say, oh, you know, my dog ate my homework.
比如，我们小时候，你会说，哦，你知道，我的狗吃了我的作业。
Right, but that really happened to me once.
对，但那真的在我身上发生过一次。
Your dog ate your homework?
你的狗吃了你的作业？
My cat ate my homework.
我的猫吃了我的作业。
Your cat ate your homework?
你的猫吃了你的作业？
Yeah.
是啊。
What did your teacher say?
你老师怎么说？
Well, actually, I was a really good student, so my teacher believed me.
嗯，其实我是个很好的学生，所以老师相信了我。
Well, my teacher wouldn't have believed me.
我老师可不会相信我。
Really?
真的吗？
No, no.
不，不。
She would have called my parents, most likely.
她很可能会给我父母打电话。
My cat really did eat my homework, and I just left it on the table, and it chewed it all
我的猫真的吃了我的作业，我就把它放在桌子上，它全给嚼了
up.
烂了。
That's weird.
真奇怪。
Why would your cat do that?
你的猫为什么会那样做？
I don't know.
我不知道。
A lot of weird excuses out there.
外面有很多奇怪的借口。
Yeah.
是啊。
I was abducted by aliens.
我被外星人绑架了。
My mom accidentally mailed my homework to Africa.
我妈妈不小心把我的作业寄到了非洲。
Really?
真的吗？
Yeah.
是的。
This happened to you?
你遇到过这种事？
Yeah.
是的。
Writing, creative excuses.
编造有创意的借口。
Well, I want to hear from our listeners.
嗯，我想听听听众们的说法。
I want to know what excuses they've used for being late with something.
我想知道他们因为什么事情迟到时用过什么借口。
So send us your excuses, send us your comments and questions.
所以请把你的借口、评论和问题发给我们。
Go to our website at EnglishPod.com, where Eric and I are always there to answer your
访问我们的网站 EnglishPod.com，我和 Eric 随时在那里回答你的
questions.
问题。
That's right, Marco, and this is an elementary lesson, right?
没错，Marco，这是一节初级课程，对吧？
Exactly.
正是。
But we also have intermediate and upper intermediate and advanced lessons for you more fluent English
但我们也有中级、中高级和高级课程，适合英语更流利的
speakers.
学习者。
Exactly.
正是。
So if you're listening to us on iTunes, be sure to visit our website and come see what
所以如果你在 iTunes 上收听我们，一定要访问我们的网站，看看
else we have to offer.
我们还提供什么。
Well, I think we're out of time, but until next time, it's goodbye.
好了，时间到了，下次再见，拜拜。